long time no see.
久しぶり
It's been a while.
久しぶりです
It's really cute.
やっぱりかわいいね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
happy.
嬉しい
Thank you for coming again.
また来てくれて
But for some reason, the camera was too far away.
でもこれもうなんか、 カメラが遠すぎて、
Have you gotten used to it?
だいぶ、 慣れてきた?
No, I might still be nervous.
いや、まだ緊張するかもしれない
It might make you nervous.
緊張するかもしれない
lie?
嘘?
It's okay to come a little closer.
ちょっと近づいていいじゃん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
What is that?
なんかその、何?
Are there cuts in your clothes again?
服はまた、切れ目入ってるの?
Also sexy.
またセクシーな
Isn't it sexy again?
またセクシーじゃないですか?
picture?
え?
what?
何?
Wait, what?
ちょっと、え?
sexy?
セクシー?
Do nothing.
何もしない
The texture of clothes.
服の生地感
What is this?
何これ?
Is it on?
ついてる?
Sparkling?
キラキラ?
It's so sparkly.
めっちゃキラキラだね
Sparkling?
キラキラ?
Does that mean it's not sparkly?
キラキラじゃないってこと?
What do you mean?
どういうこと?
You touched the glitter, right?
キラキラのとこ触っちゃったでしょ?
Sparkling?
キラキラ?
Hit it in a different place.
違うところに当たって
nice.
いいね
It's beautiful.
美しいっすね
It's cute.
可愛いっすね
I want her to be my girlfriend.
彼女にしたいくらい
Please come along.
付き合ってください
picture?
え?
Hey, me.
ちょっと、俺
I'm so happy right now, today is so good for me
俺今、あえて嬉しいからさ、 俺にとって今日はめちゃめちゃいい
By the way, has anything good happened to you recently?
日 なんだけど、 最近なんか、ちなみに何かいいことあった?
recently?
最近?
Did anything good happen?
いいことあった?
Have you recently gotten a boyfriend?
最近は、彼氏ができたこと?
Have you found a boyfriend?
彼氏ができたこと?
Yeah.
うん
Huh?
あれ?
Did you get a boyfriend?
彼氏ができた?
I got a boyfriend
彼氏ができ
Ta.
た
I do feel like I was contacted, but
確 かに、 連絡にもらった気がするけど、
It wasn't a lie.
嘘じゃなかったんだ
TRUE?
本当?
Yeah.
うん
I can't control my feelings,
気持ちを制御を追いつかないんだけど、
I can't catch up, but I'm getting to this point.
追いつかないんだけど、 でも、こういうとこ来てるんだからさ、
You're not there, right?
いないでしょ?
There is.
いる
You'll still be able to meet me in the future, right?
俺とは今後も会えるでしょ?
I feel sorry for my boyfriend,
ちょっと 彼氏に 申し訳ないから、
I wonder if I won't be able to see you again for a while.
もう ちょっと会えないかな
What's more, we met earlier, right?
おまけさ、先に会ってたじゃん?
I got a boyfriend, so I threw him away.
彼氏ができたから、 捨てる
Well then, please let me hang out with you for now.
じゃあ、俺が今はちょっと付き合ってください
Did it mean that I was making fun of myself inside?
やっぱり内心に ちょっとバカにしてたってこと?
No, I'm not making fun of you, but no,
いや、バカにしてないけど、 いや、
You're not making fun of me, are you?
バカにしてないでしょ
You're looking down on me, aren't you?
見下してるんだろ、俺のこと
I'm not looking down on you.
見下してない
It's so cute, I think I should really take care of it.
めっちゃかわいいからさ、 本当に 大事にしてあげようかなって
That's what I thought, but that's enough.
思 ったんだけどさ、 もういいや
If you're going to say something like that, then that's enough.
そんなこと言うんだったらさ、 もういいや、
You.
おまえ
I was thinking of taking care of it, but
大事にしていこうと思ってたけど、
I can't do it anymore.
もう無理だ
Hey, starting today,
おまえ、今日からさ、
What do you mean?
どう いうこと?
I wanted to cherish it, but I don't care,
大事にしたかったけど、 どうでもいいから、
Constraint processing.
制約処理
We don't have enough stomachs to deal with the constraints of us and our friends.
俺らの、 仲間たちの、 制約処理するだけの お腹の量がない
Well.
えっとね
Well, actually, there are many different men.
まあ、 今実はさ、 いろんな男たち、
I'm calling multiple guys over, for starters.
複数の男たち呼んでるからさ、 手始めにさ、
Let's do something naughty with them.
そいつらとさ、 エッチなことしよう
It's a way to get my stomach pumping.
お腹のくんりん返しってことで
Well, let's put it in, everyone.
じゃあ、入れちゃうね、みんな
Okay, come on in guys.
いいよ、入ってきてみんな
copper?
どう?
my friend
俺の友達
What do you mean?
どういうこと?
in,
で、
That's why I said it.
言 ってんじゃん、だから
From today onwards, you'll be my nako.
今日から俺のおなこなって
Oh, is it us?
あ、俺らのか
Be our nako.
俺らのおなこなって
copper?
どう?
It's cute, isn't it?
可愛いよね
After all, she's a good woman.
やっぱり、 いい女ですよね
This guy.
こいつ
Do you remember me?
覚えてる俺のこと?
I remember, now that I think about it.
覚えてる、そういえば
Yeah, yeah, I remember.
そうそうそう、覚えてる
Just a little bit.
ちょっとちょっと
Look, look.
見て見て
Do you remember?
覚えてる?
I hate it, I hate it, I hate it.
嫌だ嫌だ嫌だ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
That's sad.
悲しいな
I was really abandoned.
本当に捨てられたんだ
I don't remember.
覚えてないんだ
Well then, let's love you so much that it will remain in your memory.
じゃあさ、もっと記憶に残るくらい いっぱい愛してあげようよ、
Everyone.
みんなで
Let's do it.
やろうよ
Let's have fun.
楽しもう
Okay.
いいよ
Please stop.
やめてください
I don't like it.
嫌だ
嫌だって
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Hey hey hey.
おいおいおい
Don't run away.
逃げんなよ
Don't run away, don't run away.
逃げんな逃げんな
Let's have fun.
楽しもう
I don't like it.
嫌だ
That's terrible, you don't remember me.
ひどいよ、俺のこと覚えてないなんて
It's terrible.
ひどいよ
Seriously, don't touch it.
ひどいマジで、本当に触らないで
Seriously creepy.
本当にキモいマジで
I don't like it.
嫌だ
What do you mean, you and me?
どういうことだよ、お前、俺
Hey.
おい
What are you running away from, you?
お前何逃げてんだよ、お前
You weren't running away just now, hey.
さっき逃げてんじゃねえよ、おい
Hey.
なあ
What are you running away from?
何逃げてんの、お前
He hasn't come since a while ago.
さっきから来なかった
Our pussies are reflected in it.
俺らのおなこ映ってんだよ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Hey.
なあ
a?
あ?
What's your reply?
返事は?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
You don't need to be able to say anything but dislike, you mouth.
嫌しか言えないといらねえよ、お口
Hey.
なあ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
entertain.
楽しませる
This is what building your body is all about.
体作ってこれってさ
I want you to have fun.
楽しませろっつってんだよ
I don't like it.
嫌 だ
Don't run away anymore, I'm a nako.
もう逃げんなよ、おなこだから
Next time you run away, you're in serious trouble.
次逃げたらマジ、お前
Are you going to hit me?
お前、殴るの?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Ah.
な あ
Got it?
分かった?
What's your reply?
返事は?
The reply!
返事は!
Yes, yes.
はいわ、はいわ
Yes.
はいわ
If you hate it too much, everyone will too.
あんまり嫌がるとさ、 みんなもさ、
I'm so excited that I can't do anything, so I say it while making peace in front of the camera.
テンション上がんないからさ、 カメラの前でピースしながら言
Let's do it.
って やろ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Please show me everyone's tummies.
私をみんなのおなこ見せてくださいって
I don't like it.
嫌だ
I don't hate it.
嫌だくない
Well then, let's touch it because it will make you feel better.
じゃあ、 気持ちよくなるから、触っちゃおうかみんな
I don't like it.
嫌だ
I want to take off my clothes too, so it gets in the way.
服も脱がしたいから、 邪魔になるからさ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
She must be full of evil intentions, wearing such sexy clothes.
こんなエロい人着履いて、 悪気満々じゃん
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Look, hands, hands, hands.
ほ ら、手、手、手
Like this, like this.
こう して、こうして
Show me your bottom kiss.
下キスをよく見せて
Look, look, look.
ほら、ほら、ほら
Don't touch it.
触らない
Stop it.
やめて
I don't like it.
嫌だ
It smells so good.
すっごいいい匂い
Because I drank it.
おなこ飲んだから
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Don't cry.
涙ないで
I don't like it.
嫌だ
It feels good.
気持ちよさそう
It's a hindrance.
邪魔だ
I want to take it off.
脱がしたい
I'll take it all off.
全部脱がしちゃう
I don't like it.
嫌だ
I don't like it, I don't like it.
嫌だ嫌だ
It's a little damp.
ちょっと湿ってんじゃん
I don't like it.
嫌 だ
It's damp.
湿ってんじゃん
Seriously?
マジかよ
You can't sleep.
寝れてんじゃん
Noisy.
うるせえ
beautiful.
綺麗
As always, the food is small.
相変わらず食いとり小さいね
It's cute.
可愛いじゃん
We'll all spread it out properly.
みんなでちゃんと広げるよ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
It's a hole that will pop up once in a while.
これから一回浮かぶ穴だからね
So beautiful.
すごい綺麗
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Is it about these people?
これたちのほうか
I don't like it, I don't like it.
嫌だ嫌だ
Look carefully.
よく見してよ
To all of you.
みなさんにさ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Why do you hide it?
何で隠すの?
Open your hands.
手開けろ
I'll hide it in my tears.
涙に隠しちゃう
Let's all take a look.
み んなで見ちゃう
I don't like it.
嫌 だ
beautiful.
綺麗
I don't like it.
嫌だ
There are some great holes.
最高の穴ほどある
I don't like it.
嫌だ
So wet.
こんなに濡れて
what happened?
どうしたの?
Dislike
嫌
is.
だ
Shall we do that?
そう しようか
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Open your hands.
手を開けろ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
That's good.
いい じゃん
It's in full view.
丸見えだぞ
Let's all spread the word.
みんな広げようぜ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Double peace.
ダブルピースしろ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Peace.
ピースしろ
ピースしろよ
Please take a look.
見てくださいって
Take a proper picture on camera.
ちゃんとカメラに撮って
I don't like it.
嫌だ
I have to say it properly.
ちゃんと言わないと
Please check on everyone's health.
み んなのおなほの具合を確認してください
That's not the case.
そういうことはない
Let's check.
確認しよう
I don't like it.
嫌だ
It'll fit a lot.
いっぱい入るじゃん
I don't like it.
嫌だ
It's really tight.
すごい締めてる
I don't like it.
嫌だ
How many pieces does it fit?
何本入るんだ?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
How many books do you have now?
今何本だ?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
I'll build up my muscles.
筋肉してやるよ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Wake up.
体を起こして
It feels good.
気持ちいいな
You're tightening your stomach.
お腹締めてるじゃん
I don't like it.
嫌 だ
good
好
I guess that's it.
き なんだな、やっぱり
Isn't that frustrating?
悔しいじゃねえかよ
Which one feels better?
どっちが気持ちいいんだよ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Is it this way?
こっちかな?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
It's too heavy, it's too heavy.
重すぎだよ、重すぎ
It's time consuming.
手間まつるじゃん
I don't like it.
嫌だ
What is it?
何だっけ?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
嫌
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Emperor of the country.
国の帝王
I don't like it.
嫌 だ
Is the rice delicious?
ご飯おいしい?
delicious.
美味しい
I don't like it.
嫌だ
That's right, you want to see dicks.
そうそう、ちんこ見たいだろ
I don't like it.
嫌
Either look at dicks or kiss everyone.
ちんこ見るか、全員とキスするか、
Which one?
どっちだよ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
A kiss in the morning?
朝、キスか
You know, it's just right with everyone.
ほら、全員とちょうどいいよ
A kiss.
キス合わせ
キ ス 合わせ
Chew with uncle.
おじさんとチューしろ
Hey, keep chewing.
ほ ら、まだチューしろ
Not yet.
まだだよ
Uncle is coming.
おじさん来るぞ
cute.
可愛い
I don't like it.
嫌だ
nice.
いいね
I'm happy.
幸せだな
Okay.
いいよ
Get rid of your boyfriend and go out with me.
彼氏とはかれて、俺と付き合ってくれ
Please.
頼むよ
Stop kissing me passionately like lovers.
恋人みたいに熱いキスしてやめろ
I hope we get along well.
付き合いいんだったらね
It's as good as a kiss.
キスくらいいいだろ
Hmm.
うーん
There are many.
たくさんあるよ
You can choose as much as you want.
選び放題だよ
A lot will come.
いっぱい来るぞ
Chat about whatever you like.
どれでも好きなおしゃべり
My favorite chat.
好きなおしゃべり
Turn to me and repeat with both hands.
こっち向いて、両手リピースしろ
Turn your face sideways.
顔を横
Yeah.
うん
Peace, peace.
ピース、ピース
I'm glad there are 6 of them.
嬉しいじゃん、6本もあってさ
That's right.
そうだよ
You must be happy.
嬉しいだろ
I don't like it.
嫌
I can't go on my own, from here.
自分でいかないな、こっちから
Come on, sit here.
ほらほら、こっちに座って
Hey, open your mouth.
おい、口開けろ
Open this, hey.
こっち開けろ、おい
Please suck it yourself.
自分からしゃぶらしてください
Hmm.
うーん
Aren't you sucking?
しゃぶってないのか?
Make me feel good.
気持ちよくしてよ
Next, next, look.
次、次、ほら
Hey, hey, hey.
ほらほら、ほらほら
I need to feel good.
気持ちよくしないと
Look, look.
ほらほら
Please suck this too.
こっちもしゃぶってくれよ
こ っちもしゃぶってくれよ
Here, suck it.
ほら、しゃぶってよ
This is terrible, remember this?
ひどいよ、覚えてるだろ、これ
You remember this chink.
このチンク覚えてるだろ
Why don't you lick me?
なんで舐めてくんないの?
It's terrible.
ひどいよ
Here, suck it.
ほ ら、しゃぶって
Look, look.
ほら、ほら
Well, look.
ちゃんと、ほら
Make yourself feel good, come on.
気持ちよくしてよ、ほら
Come on, let's move our mouths ourselves.
ほら、自分で口を動かそう
I think everyone's chinks are the same.
みんなのチンク、一致にしたと思うから
Hey, everyone gather around, hey, hey.
ほら、みんな集まって、ほらほら
Get together.
集まって
Which one is better?
どれがいいの?
Which one did you do best?
どれが一番上手かった?
Okay, choose.
いいぞ、選んで
I'm telling you to choose.
選べって言ってんの
Hey, which tink is the best?
ほら、どのチンクが一番いいの?
Well, look carefully.
ほら、よく見て
Look, look.
ほらほら
Choose the one that looks the biggest, for now.
一番デカそうなの選べよ、とりあえず
Anything is fine.
なんでもいいよ
There you go.
ほら、それ
oh,
おー、
Emperor's Chinku.
帝 王のチンク
Is this good?
これ が いいの?
Look.
ほら
Yay!
やったー
You chose it yourself, right?
自分で選んだんだろ?
It's your favorite tincture, right?
自分のね、好みのチンクなんでしょ?
This tink was good, right?
このチンクがよかったんでしょ?
Take your time and enjoy it.
じっくり味わいながらさ
Is this the end?
これ終わり?
Is this cute?
これ、かわれ?
Well, in addition.
ほら、加えて
Look.
ほら
Do you remember?
思い出した?
It's time for my favorite cock.
一番大好きなチンポの時だよ
You like this, right?
これ 好きなんでしょ?
This cock is the best.
この チンポが一番
Okay, so so so so so so so so so so so so so such.
いいよ、そらそらそら
please.
どうぞ
Can I stop?
やめていいかわ
No, stop.
やだ、止め
No way.
やだ
That's fine.
いいだろ
No way.
やだ
Because my feet are wide.
足 広いから
No way.
やだ
No, no.
やだ、やだ
Someone hold my legs.
誰 か足持って
No, no.
やだ、やだ
That's amazing.
生すげーな
No way.
やだ
Yes, it will be full.
はい、いっぱいれちゃうぞ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいかな
Mom, you are the best mom.
お母さん、最高のお母さんだよ、お前は
It helps a lot inside too.
中にも助かるね、たくさん
I'll give you a lot later.
後でいっぱい出してやるから
I'll give you a lot.
た くさん出してやるよ
There's going to be a lot of chumpo, dude.
いっぱいチュンポ来るぞ、おい
Let's all take turns, take turns.
みんな順番に入れようぜ、順番に
Let's put them in order.
順番に入れようぜ
You haven't forgotten this face, have you?
こっちの顔、忘れてないよね?
You haven't forgotten, have you?
忘れてないよね?
copper?
どう?
Do you remember?
覚えてる?
Looks like it'll be out soon as usual.
相変わらずすぐ出そうだよ
Do you remember?
思い出した?
Look, who's next?
ほら、次、誰だよ
Everyone in, everyone.
お全員入れろ、お全員
Let's change our position.
体勢変えようぜ
Move your hands properly.
ちゃんと手を動かして
Let's change our position.
体勢変えようぜ
Finish it properly.
ちゃんと仕上げて
ちゃんと仕上げてよ
Because you can get on top of me.
上に乗ってもらえるから
I don't want to get too excited.
興奮しすぎたくない
Calm down, calm down.
落ち着け、落ち着け
Let's put them in order.
順番に入れようぜ
Can I take it out today?
今日出していい?
Was it bad when I took it out?
出したらダメだった?
It was no good.
ダメだった
It's not out, right?
出てないでしょ
Well, okay.
まあまあ、いい
I was also concerned about what was behind me.
後ろ、後ろも気になって
No, no.
いや、ダメだよ
Today is a dangerous day.
今日は危ない日だよ
It's a dangerous day.
危ない日だよ
Because.
だって
That's fine.
いいじゃん
It's a dangerous day, but don't fix it.
危ない日なんだけど、直さないで
I need to properly neutralize the next spirit.
次の精神、ちゃんと中和しないとな
Make yourself feel good.
気持ちよくしろよ
Everyone sit down.
みんなで座ってよ
If you don't need it yourself, do it yourself.
自分でいらないと、自分で
Well then, okay.
じゃあ、いいよ
Fallen asleep.
寝込まれて
So, are you going to sleep too?
じゃあ、こっちも寝込むのか?
Your butt is big and beautiful.
お尻、大きくてきれいだな
Open your legs properly.
ちゃんと足を開いて
Oh no, I might not be able to hold back any time soon.
やばい、俺もそろそろ我慢できないかもしれない
Today isn't the first time.
今日が初めてじゃないんだから
I'll put it out.
出すよ
It's a dangerous day, so no.
危ない日だから、ダメ
I'll be grateful if you let me know next time.
次から出してもらったら、ありがとうございます
Let's be thankful to each and every one of you.
一人一人、ちゃんと感謝しよう
Let's go.
行くぞ
What does that mean?
どういうことだろう?
I guess they let you out?
出してもらったんだろう?
Thank you very much.
ありがとうですよ
thank you.
ありがとうございます
You can say it.
言えるじゃねえか
Today is a dangerous day.
今日危ない日なんだって
Well then, let's have a baby for the old man.
じゃあ、おじさんの子供を作ろうか
Quickly, quickly.
早 く、早く
早く、早く
Move, now.
動くんだ、すぐ
I didn't die in my sleep.
寝死したんじゃねえ
No more.
もう、やだ
I can sleep.
寝れるよ
Yes, please.
はい、頼む
I'll be using it a lot from now on.
これからいっぱい使ってあげます